[{"answer": "What's that", "docId": "Meet_John_Doe.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "What letter", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "The letter", "docId": "Meet_John_Doe.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "The letter from my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " In what man", "docId": "Meet_John_Doe.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "What my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " Very pretty. Very pretty, indeed, my friend. But would you mind telling me who goes on Christmas Eve", "docId": "Meet_John_Doe.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " What my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Huh", "docId": "Meet_John_Doe.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Yeah, I'm all right", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I seen plenty of fellers start out with fifty bucks and wind up with a bank account", "docId": "Meet_John_Doe.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " And let me tell you, my friend. When you become a guy with a bank account, they got you.  Yes sir, they got you", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " Hey, whatsa matter with a bank account, anyway", "docId": "Meet_John_Doe.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Who's got him", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Give away", "docId": "Meet_John_Doe.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Say, he's giving it away! I'm gonna get me some of that", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "And the fifty's all gone, huh? Who's the ten for", "docId": "Meet_John_Doe.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "The Websters", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Wait a minute. my friend don't wanta sign no autographs", "docId": "Meet_John_Doe.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What does he do all day?  He's writin' out his memories", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Yep. There was a major league scout there watching me, too. And he came down after the game with a contract. Do you know what?  I couldn't life my arm to sign it. But I'll be okay again as soon as I get it fixed up", "docId": "Meet_John_Doe.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What do you mean, too bad", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "This is no time for cheap publicity, Mr. my friend", "docId": "Meet_John_Doe.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " That's fine, honey. Now, get out", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Look, Mr. my friend, I think you've got a lot of nerve having those people hold us here", "docId": "Meet_John_Doe.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Well, if there's nobody holding us here, let's get going. Incidentally, my name isn't my friend. It's my friend", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Well, I'll be doggoned if over forty people don't show up. 'Course none of us knew what to do, but we sure got a kick out of seeing how glad everybody was just to say hello to one another", "docId": "Meet_John_Doe.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Oh, yeah. We made Sourpuss chairman and decided to call ourselves The that place. And, say, incidentally, this is my wife. Come here, honey", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Flowers", "docId": "Meet_John_Doe.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "She isn't", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Don't worry about that", "docId": "Meet_John_Doe.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Didn't I tell you that everybody in this room would be taken care? My agreement with you gentlemen stands", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "It must be some kind of a gag", "docId": "Meet_John_Doe.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "A gag. A gag", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "That's got nothing to do with it", "docId": "Meet_John_Doe.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Yes! I was paid! But th", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "What difference does that make", "docId": "Meet_John_Doe.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "No, I didn't write it, bu", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Meet_John_Doe.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": " I ain't seen him for a week", "qsentId": 40}]